<modDesc descVersion="106">
    <author>Ritter</author>
    <version>1.0.1.0</version>
    <title>
        <en>More Visual Animals - Ritter version</en>
        <de>Mehr Visuelle Tiere - Ritter Version</de>
        <fr>Animaux Plus Visuels - Version Ritter</fr>
    </title>
    <description>
        <en>
            <![CDATA[ This is a modified version of the More Visual Animals mod by Arrow-kb, a standalone module from RealisticLivestock.

Increases the visual animal cap to 200 per placeable. Does nothing if RealisticLivestock is enabled. Slider to change the max limit of visual animals can be accessed with Shift+T.

Singleplayer only.

Features:
- Up to 200 visible animals per husbandry
- In-game slider (Shift+T) to adjust the visual animal limit
- Recommended button suggests a limit based on your PC's performance profile
- Settings persist across sessions
- Automatically disables when RealisticLivestock is active

Changes from the original mod:
- Fixed compatibility with other mods that hook into vehicle enter logic (e.g. CabCinematic).

Source code: https://github.com/rittermod/FS25_MoreVisualAnimalsRM

Changelog

1.0.1.0:
- First Ritter release (based on More Visual Animals by Arrow-kb)
- Fixed compatibility with other mods that hook into vehicle enter logic (e.g. CabCinematic)

1.0.0.1:
- Original More Visual Animals mod by Arrow-kb
]]>
        </en>
        <de>
            <![CDATA[ Dies ist eine modifizierte Version des More Visual Animals Mods von Arrow-kb, ein eigenständiges Modul von RealisticLivestock.

Erhöht die Anzahl der sichtbaren Tiere pro Platzierung auf 200. Hat keine Wirkung, wenn RealisticLivestock aktiviert ist. Der Schieberegler zum Ändern der maximalen Anzahl sichtbarer Tiere kann mit Shift+T aufgerufen werden.

Nur Einzelspieler.

Funktionen:
- Bis zu 200 sichtbare Tiere pro Tierhaltung
- Schieberegler im Spiel (Shift+T) zum Anpassen der Anzahl sichtbarer Tiere
- Empfohlen-Taste schlägt ein Limit basierend auf dem Leistungsprofil deines PCs vor
- Einstellungen bleiben über Sitzungen hinweg erhalten
- Deaktiviert sich automatisch, wenn RealisticLivestock aktiv ist

Änderungen gegenüber dem Originalmod:
- Kompatibilitätsproblem mit anderen Mods behoben, die sich in die Fahrzeug-Einstiegslogik einklinken (z.B. CabCinematic).

Quellcode: https://github.com/rittermod/FS25_MoreVisualAnimalsRM

Änderungsprotokoll

1.0.1.0:
- Erste Ritter-Version (basierend auf More Visual Animals von Arrow-kb)
- Kompatibilität mit anderen Mods behoben, die sich in die Fahrzeug-Einstiegslogik einklinken (z.B. CabCinematic)

1.0.0.1:
- Original More Visual Animals Mod von Arrow-kb
]]>
        </de>
        <fr>
            <![CDATA[ Ceci est une version modifiée du mod More Visual Animals d'Arrow-kb, un module autonome de RealisticLivestock.

Augmente la limite visuelle d'animaux à 200 par emplacement. N'a aucun effet si RealisticLivestock est activé. Le curseur permettant de modifier la limite maximale d'animaux visibles est accessible à l'aide de la combinaison de touches Shift+T.

Solo uniquement.

Fonctionnalités:
- Jusqu'à 200 animaux visibles par élevage
- Curseur en jeu (Shift+T) pour ajuster la limite d'animaux visibles
- Bouton Recommandé suggère une limite basée sur le profil de performance de votre PC
- Les paramètres sont conservés entre les sessions
- Se désactive automatiquement lorsque RealisticLivestock est actif

Modifications par rapport au mod original:
- Correction de la compatibilité avec d'autres mods qui modifient la logique d'entrée dans les véhicules (ex. CabCinematic).

Code source: https://github.com/rittermod/FS25_MoreVisualAnimalsRM

Journal des modifications

1.0.1.0:
- Première version Ritter (basée sur More Visual Animals par Arrow-kb)
- Correction de la compatibilité avec d'autres mods qui modifient la logique d'entrée dans les véhicules (ex. CabCinematic)

1.0.0.1:
- Mod original More Visual Animals par Arrow-kb
]]>
        </fr>
    </description>
    <iconFilename>icon_MoreVisualAnimals.dds</iconFilename>
    <multiplayer supported="false"/>
    <extraSourceFiles>
        <sourceFile filename="scripts/RLMedium.lua"/>
    </extraSourceFiles>
    <l10n filenamePrefix="translations/translation"/>
    <inputBinding>
        <actionBinding action="mva_VisualAnimalsDialog">
            <binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_lshift KEY_t"/>
        </actionBinding>
    </inputBinding>
    <actions>
        <action name="mva_VisualAnimalsDialog"/>
    </actions>
</modDesc>